<resources>
    <string name="about_text1">
        Legend of the lost chef is a dungeon seek and find adventure-game. It contains no violance, even though there is a sword button for swinging the sword. The original plan was to make a hack-n-slash game, but since I made this kinds of games before I instead added characters that you can interact with and talk with to make the story more alive.
    </string>
    <string name="about_text2">
How to play:\n
You draw a walking vector in the direction you want to walk.
Where you start or end the vector does not matter. Only the direction of the vector matters.\n
\n
You can talk with characters by walking up to them. You can also swing your sword with the sword button, but this is as mentioned only a special effect for fun\n
\n
Win condition\n
The game ends when you have successfully found and rescued the Chef that is gone\n




    </string>
        <string name="about_text3">
About the developer\n
\n
This game was made by Erik Gustafsson as a final project for a course in Android Game development at Högskola Kristianstad. Erik is a 28 years old master student in computer science from Uppsala


\n\n
Erik developed all the code in this game. The graphics and sounds come from third party online resources
</string>
<string name="credits">
Sprite graphics:\n
Reiners Tilesets\n
http://www.reinerstilesets.de/\n
\n
Textures:\n
http://www.cgtextures.com/\n
\n
Sound effect(sword):\n
http://freesound.org/people/audione/sounds/52458/\n
\n
Music:\n
Preziosa Overture by Carl Maria von Weber\n
Lived 1786-1826 in Germany
    </string>
    <string name="game_title">Legend of the lost chef</string>
    <string name="app_name">Lost Chef</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">SplashActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_menu">MenuActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">AboutActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_credits">CreditsActivity</string>
</resources>


